Hello, hello, hello everyone. This is a class of Ya Man Jiu.
Now it's our second episode of MD Little Skills.
In the first episode, the first little skill, let's talk about how to quickly delete the inner line.
For example, this dress has been painted by me a lot of inner lines.
Then we don't want this line.
Then how do we quickly delete it?
Generally speaking, the selection is deleted by the whole version.
Then at this time, we just need to double click this line.
Then after double clicking, double click again.
Then we just press the delete button.
It can be deleted completely.
Similarly, let's take a look at this pants.
After double clicking, double click again.
Then press the delete button to delete it.